Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial, 154271
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154275; (34 audiocassettes)
        - NMA 5, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506721)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&af2e3b73-21f7-4a78-a766-6cc5fdcdb2f1
        - Crissements Sous La Roue Du Temps, 1985; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:19:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506747)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&def5bae6-ccaa-4048-9441-9d521afcbcac
        - Bouche, Thierry. L'information du jour, 1988-1989; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:59:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506754)
          1. Salut à toi, Nancarrow, 3' 26"
          2. Jubilée, 7'
          3. Tout Electre, 2' 35"
          4. J'y croix ?, 4' 55"
          5. Le temps qu'il fait, 6' 55"
          6. L'état, 3' 30"
          1. Vers le noir, 5' 50"
          2. Coucou, Purcell, 3' 45"
          3. La bouche, 5' 15"
          4. Profanations/Permutations, 11' 45"
          5. Novi Sad, 3' 30"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5590e5a1-de66-4ce4-8fb4-4e5b5934ca95
        - Hammersley, Richard. "Lobby Newsletter 16", 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:22:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506739)
          essential style
          ae wake
          interview - Richard Hammersley to yz
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dbafd6b3-8b56-4416-bd84-e96348e1f957
        - Gaburo "Antiphony VIII", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:16:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506762)
          (Révolution) percussion: Steve Schiele
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&cfaec5d6-06c5-4451-9dd1-9cd9628a172f
        - Dreyfus, Charles and Papp, Tibor. Le Trou Noir 84, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:04:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506770)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0d0957db-b23a-4fec-8387-953124f23585
        - Polkinhorn, Harry., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:30:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506788)
          1. Wer
          2. Water
          3. Man
          4. Wind
          5. Pneu
          6. Speak
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&38e25826-0878-4ddd-beaf-7cfa5a1095c7
        - Nitnelav, Tumla. Trout 1-5 / ...11, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:28:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Program distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506796)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dd9ff644-6b1d-4710-bb77-233925052292
        - Scherstjanoi, Valeri. Polyphonia, 1991; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:34:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506804)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d6da1e3e-5b64-4475-9e35-1af8bbcf7cd1
        - Heidsieck, Bernard. Poésie Sonore, "Canal Street", 1985; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:57:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506812)
          This appears to be a duplicate.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&227160f3-c361-4b2e-831b-31cabbfc0e31
        - Le livre sonore / Le sonosaure, 1987; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:26:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506820)
          Kinkao (14' 22")
          Petites orgues (7' 28")
          Tribal (7' 28")
          Queiques formules utiles (6' 34")
          Ad-delà des macines (7' 14")
          S'abolir sonore (14' 30")
          Rire construit (4' 50")
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1e56940c-c66a-4581-8b7e-cf9b507b826a
        - Pastior, Oskar. Der Krimgotische Fächer, 1978, 1979; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:54:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506846)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&996da01b-e3d0-4028-8cce-88f332af4ce8
        - Beckett, Samuel. Poémes suivi de Mirlitonnades / Imagination Morte Imaginez Bing, 1984; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:34:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506853)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&cc2cabc6-3984-48b6-bab8-15fa8db01955
        - Hudak, John., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:02:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506861)
          "Clarity"
          "Pleasantly with Me"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&650de5d1-6989-4309-9b58-fc56c08e0c56
        - Higgins, Dick. Sound Poetry, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:31:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506879)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&923b09f7-79bc-4572-bf2b-40d9f4a0d04d
        - Tardos, Anne. New Wilderness Audiographics, "Gatherings", 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506887)
          There is a handwritten message included with the audiocassette. It reads: For the great Chopin with best wishes and friendship, Anne Tardos, Stockholm 1984-04-15
          "Refrigerator Defrosting", 1975, 14' 7"
          "Seven-Layer Song", 1980, 4'
          "Voices from Video", 1980-81, 5' 5"
          "Pipes at 110 Mercer, November 1974", 13' 30"
          "Real Sleeper, Real Dreamer", 1976, 9' 52"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a0029f17-0ee7-4c24-88ff-ff9da499f01a
        - Hammersley, Richard. "Lobby Newsletter 16", 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:22:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506895)
          This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e45d98f9-6fe2-44d6-a678-25fd22606d79
        - Reviuw Parade-Interrationale. La Pote Au Japon!, 1987 September; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:57:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506903)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1029911d-78e4-4d84-974b-c6f50402d5fc
        - Wendt, Larry. "The Remembrance of a Technological Past", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506911)
          "Where I Am From"
          "The South Bay Homebrew Inventors Club"
          "Muffie"
          "Toad Farming For Profit"
          "Silicon Valley Ghost Town"
          "The Great Silicon Valley Toad Plague"
          "Gene Cot Toad"
          "Silicon Valley Horror Story"
          "Silicon Valley Love Story"
          "The End of San Jose"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&512dae3a-2e82-4004-90e8-4faaa6c3431f
        - Schwerner, Armand. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:56:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506929)
          "the triumph of the will"
          "Tablets 15-19"
          "the work"
          "Bacchae Sonnets"
          "the joy of Sven Hedin"
          "Bar Mitzvah for Adam"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1c04d1a2-ae4d-4f90-a5ed-86c883787c0e
        - Vizents, A. Furniture, 1982 June 7; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:15:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506937)
          "Wood Chair"
          "Couch"
          "Upholstered Chair"
          "Wardrobe"
          "Venetian Blind"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&00b3b371-17be-4249-a583-34cefaf220a6
        - Bertozzi, Gabriela-Aldo. La Signora Proteo, 1993; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:09:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506945)
          Bertozzi, G-A. "Ouverture"
          Mattioli, G. "Monologo finale"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&049bc4b3-be9e-4b35-85e5-01a8e66a87ef
        - Kagel, Mauricio. (Hörspiel) Ein Aufnahmezustand / Der Tribun, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:37:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506952)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ce12588b-acc9-4b63-b2f3-c83942e9a4e9
        - "La Nouvelle Revue D'Art Moderne", 1980 January; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:19:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio levels vary from 35:36-39:30. The left channel of audio is silent from 1:13:02-1:15:03. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506960)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c505c0e1-049d-4c26-bc97-0c864723945e
        - Curtay, Jean-Paul. Body Music 1, 1980; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:23:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506838)
          Cage, John. Introduction to Jean-Paul Curtay's performance
          What is Body Music?
          Teasing Release (7' 56")
          Abirdment (18' 54")
          Anatomy of the bodily sound (15' 19")
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a1f5c93d-c4fd-40a2-b20d-43d08e9ad8ac
        - Media-Space, 1982 July 6; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:31:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506978)
          "So No No"
          "Worker Worble"
          "Factual Physical"
          "March Fly"
          "Mediation"
          "Double Double"
          "Driving Around"
          "Coming and Going"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&032ce961-9720-4133-b31f-de44019a88d3
        - Media-Space, 1982 August 12; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:25:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506986)
          Thomas, Paul. "Simulcast"
          Vizents, A. "Get Me"
          Thomas, Paul. "Think Nothing of It"
          Vizents, A. "Scratching"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09cb07e7-a6db-4fe6-adfe-40f1e8b5297b
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154274; (34 audiocassettes)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e0146191-b03b-487b-8081-eeb6b9bd2ee5
        - Chopin, Henri., 1983; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:50:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507463)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3afb55be-e851-4b9c-83a1-29e4d3df9d17
        - Maillard, Claude. "La Contadora", 1984; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:45:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507471)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ec0bd6ef-d262-446b-bea2-0c4c5b8e8c4d
        - Seuphor, Michel., undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:42:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. Audio on the left channel is recorded at a lower volume from 42:23 until the end of the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507489)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7180369a-188c-46ac-ac2d-c9a5381236eb
        - Helyer, Nigel. "Siren Song", 1992; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:29:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507497)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e1588c52-e75e-4e61-8b0a-8d627d7e06f9
        - De Vree, Paul. "poemi audio-visuali', 1970; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:26:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507505)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c273a98c-9322-4753-b081-4cec906c9af2
        - Singh, Gary. "Works with Jerks", 1992-1994; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:49:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507513)
          "My Name is Not Ed"
          "TORNtables"
          "Kataklysmos"
          "Problems of Ambience"
          "The Fugitive"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&925a38f4-5e5f-4d4a-96cc-f4f8b46864e6
        - Meyer, Peter R. "Nattövning / Ektoplasma", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio sounds unclear at times on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507521)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&40bbc2f8-2520-4775-9aa6-715916764f58
        - Hammersley and Tabor. "The 4-Day Opportunity", 1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507539)
          A Theory of Dancing
          W --__(h)
          [Roem] Studies Volume 1
          Loam
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&37295bb4-108f-404b-ad1a-b1b7031bb5b8
        - A poem by H. Chopin / Akenaton...The bio, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; This audiocassette is blank. The tape has not been digitized. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507547)
        - Paté de Voix 4, 1990; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507554)
          Torino, gennaio
          Chopin, Henri. "Chuiantantes et Répits", 7' 42"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Percolator", 30"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Improvised Caesuras", 2' 45"
          Keppler, Joseph. "U.S.S. Ohio", 1' 50"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Timepiece", 15"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Communication", 1' 40"
          bpNichol. "senza titolo", 1' 40"
          byNichol. "senza titolo", 2' 27"
          bpNichol. "And this is what it means when meaning's over", 6' 40"
          Bouche, Thierry. (pour Bob & Nèv) "Tout électre", 2' 37"
          Heidsieck, Bernard. "Derviche / Le Robert" (Lettre "B"), 6'
          Valsher. "da 'autgedichte' ", 6' 42"
          Wendt, Larry. "Number 4", 8' 22"
          Bertola, C. and Vitacchio, A. "Adattarsi", 7' 35"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2b3d5d54-5245-4672-91e2-fe7401828108
        - Damen, Herman. "verbosonies", 1970; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:33:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507562)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ae86ac2e-fd1d-4e0a-abed-084e6e1e4758
        - Andersen, Eric. "The Crying Place", 1991 June 18 to 1991 July 13; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. A high amount of hiss can be heard. The audio is sometimes unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507570)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1b7c98e9-4a99-4477-8583-6749f095d680
        - Sarenco. "political poems', 1970; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:18:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507588)
          "Kein Gott" (1970)
          "Papa Zum" (1968-1970)
          "Homage to Lin Piao (1970)
          "Bisturi Poem" (1970)
          "Screditare Le Autorità Borghesi!" (1970)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c269db1e-b666-4df1-9252-5fa2ec061804
        - "Audio Eyes", 1983; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:31:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507596)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&072cf93c-a02d-4c81-b56d-62f544990cd2
        - Rothenberg, Jerome. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:37:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507604)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5ed000a5-c131-45d9-abde-de294444c351
        - Word Theatre Soundpoetry, 1965-1995; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:27:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507612)
          International Exhibition in Koenigsberg
          1. Scherstjanoi, Valeri, Horn, Ernest and Czukay, Holger. "Das Radio Der zukunft"
          2. Claus, Carlfriedrich. "Lautaggregat"
          3. Kolomijtsev, Andrei. "Asphaltstrasse"
          8. Dutton, Paul. "Stereo Head" and "Kit-Talk"
          9. Bulatov, Dmitry. "Russian Folk Noism" and "Life with machine"
          10. Riedl, Josef Anton. "Vielleicht ist es so" and "Paper Musik II"
          11. Chopin, Henri. Dialogue
          12. Mon, Franz. "Montage aus "artikulationen 62"
          13. Vinogradov, German, Kravchenko, Alexsei, and Meinkov, Willi R. "Kwakuum"
          14. Hutchinson, Brenda. "Long Tube Trio"
          15. Cobbing, Bob. "From ABC to Sound (d-p-t)"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2755ad99-bdae-449c-9e0d-bc71a8181fc5
        - Meyer, Peter R. Nattövning/P, 1982 June; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:32:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507620)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&df3f8548-3909-4da1-98bd-06f9113e94fa
        - Bissett, Bill. "Northern Birds in Color", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507638)
          "hunee sound chant"
          "his vois was going out uv nim"
          "jed bi kor bensk trik"
          "how uy know"
          "riff th veil from my eyes"
          "ther may have bin a tunnel"
          "in yr life"
          "alpha"
          "awake in th red desert"
          "wand ring"
          "normal is not returning"
          "th magic lure uv sea shells"
          "sound chant"
          "farrago 79"
          "th centr is th belly button"
          "victoria si eeee:"
          "th lifting hands"
          "th wun with th glasses"
          "th unicorn is loos"
          "i gotta feelin"
          "chant"
          "collingwood"
          "Yu want to walk with me (asking) may all thees blessings"
          "england scotland nd wales"
          "blew horizon"
          "hunee chant..."
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7abc9da3-7232-4b65-9f07-32fca0bfe05b
        - Gruppo 70. "poemi tecnologici", 1965-1971; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower volume. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507646)
          Marcucci, Lucia. "poesia auditiva"
          Miccini, Eugenio. "concerto per armi, vox humana a varia tecnologia"
          Ori, Luciano. "situazione bianca PTF-1"
          Perfetti, Michele. "poema inglobante"
          Pignotti, Lamberto. "il re dei pagliacci"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b9f64e4f-9ca1-4fbe-b255-2146628e14b4
        - Bak, Eleonore. Ton Arbeiten, "Ohne Titel", 1987; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:12:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507653)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a8a178d2-0ef0-45ed-aa43-628d3ad955fd
        - Supranormal, 1983; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:53:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507661)
          A list of contents on the audiotape are included. Side two is attributed to Lee Harwood.
          1. Editorial/Introduction
          2. Brown, Paul. "Startled"
          3. Sheppard, Robert G. "The Lover"
          4. Woods, Greg. "The Lemon Blossom and the Cat"
          5. Chopin, Henri. "Throat Power"
          6. Row, John. "Judas Poe M"
          7. Griffiths, Bill. "Found Texts"
          a. "Found Text on Rochester"
          b. "Found Text"
          c. "Found Sea Texts"
          d. "Ode to Autumn"
          8. Henri, Adrian. "Mrs. Albion You've Got a Lovely Daughter"
          1. "Chen"
          2. "Animal Days"
          3. "Triangulation of Points A, B, C."
          4. "Portraits 1-4"
          5. "Boston Spring"
          6. "Quasida"
          7. "The Long Black Veil (Book Six)" and "Three Trans-Tristan Tzara"
          8. "Approach"
          9. "For Robert Desnos"
          10. "Good Time 2"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&51f76dfb-2a10-4893-b717-a6d71462994c
        - Rühm, Gerhard. "Wintermärchen", 1976 December; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:17:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507679)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fca88547-7543-4292-aeee-f1674a6b05fa
        - McCaffery, Steve. "research on the mouth", 1977-1978; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507687)
          "S.I.S.M.A." (Movements 1 & 2)
          "Portraits 1-34"
          "S 1 Z 2 Z 1 E 1 R 2 Z 3"
          "Names for Cricket"
          "Structure of Incident"
          "A Little Valentine"
          "Pleasant Ode for Vincent Trasov"
          "S.I.S.M.A." (Movement 3)
          "Aupe Relationships"
          "Black Aleph" (1 & 2)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&eee66ba0-54e5-4a86-b962-6c74dc50028a
        - Collin, Françoise and Seyrig, Delphine. "Anne, Ma Soeur Anne", 1973?; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:26:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507695)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0a7759e0-95e5-4c47-b587-16318c2bab58
        - Nitsch, Hermann. Orgelkonzert, 1986 December 9; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507703)
          A list of contents are included with this audiocassette.
          "die geburt des dionysos"
          "die tiefe des alls"
          "die tiefe des alls (Forsetzung)"
          "der hirschgott"
          "dornenkrönung"
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&549ae682-cd0d-40c5-a3d5-1a6c6b1fbafd
        - Mac Low, Jackson. "Homage to Leona Bleiweiss", 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:02:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507711)
          New Wilderness Audiographics
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c6d9f368-e43e-4257-9ca2-931ae51f87be
        - Dana, Llys and Marlow, Jack. "Court Circuit", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:18:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507729)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&04bc71e1-1209-4b59-a77a-56e621c9fdd8
        - Chopin, Henri. "Le Voyage Labio - Velaire" / "Le Cri", 1971 August - September; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:15:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio in the right channel is silent from 00:05-01:09 and again at the end of the program. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507737)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bde05449-514e-448e-8e95-96c47f7ae6a8
        - Taliesin and Dana, Llys. "Hautension" / "Alkaest", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:00:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507745)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c0bd6089-131c-42d5-9654-1216a7701d5c
        - Flynt, Henry. "You Are My Everlovin'" / "Celestial Power", 1980-1981; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:27:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507752)